Guide to the A.I.R. Gallery Archives MSS.184
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Exhibition files
  - Subseries A: Exhibitions held at A.I.R. (see also Oversize)
    - "National Members Exhibition", Sept. 7-25, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 695)
    - Sue Hettmansperger/Mary Kramer, Sep. 28-Oct. 16, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 696)
    - Nancy Storrow/Brenda Garand/"Subway Art: A Dialogue between Faith Ringgold and Nancy Spero" (Feb. 21), Oct. 19-Nov. 6, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 697)
    - Ann Pachner/Betsey Garand, Nov. 9-Dec. 4, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 698)
    - "National Members Group Show"/Helen Golden and Judith Moncrieff, Dec. 7, 1999-Jan. 2, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 699)
    - "Turning Points: Gallery Artists' Exhibition", Jan. 4-22, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 700)
    - Beatrice Riese/Cecily Kahn, Jan. 25-Feb. 12, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 701)
    - "Generations II: Women Artists in the New Millennium", Feb. 15-Mar. 11, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 702)
    - "Generations II: Women Artists in the New Millennium", Feb. 15-Mar. 11, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 702a.)
    - "Generations II: Women Artists in the New Millennium" - silent auction sales invoices, Feb. 15-Mar. 11, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 702b.)
    - Carolyn Martin/Margaret Jean, Mar. 14-Apr. 1, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 703)
    - Susan Bee/Rachel Banai, Apr. 4-22, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 704)
    - Group Show: "Illuminata"/Kathy Karant, Apr. 25-May 13, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 705)
    - Laetitia Hohenberg/Jo Ganter, May 16-June 3, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 706)
    - Mimi Wlodarczyk/Ruth Eckland and Marta Thoma, June 6-27, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 707)
    - Asian American Women Artists Alliance: "Eat Art 3", Sep. 9, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 708)
    - "National Members Exhibition" (Galleries I + II), Sep. 12-Oct. 7, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 709)
    - Jessie Nebraska Gifford/Julie Wosk, Oct. 10-Nov. 4, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 710)
    - Louise Kramer/Alexandra McCagg, Nov. 7-Dec. 2, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 711)
    - Juri Kim, "Aspiration of Silence", Dec. 5-31, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 712)
    - Debra Hampton, "Technically Engaged", Jan. 2-27, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 713)
    - Affiliates/Sheila Manion-Artz and Lauren Weinger, Jan. 30-Feb. 24, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 714)
      [nb: contains 2 compact discs, annotated: "Lauren Weinger A.I.R. 2001 Portraits + Places 1. Silo Interior 2. Silo Exterior 3. Recollections 4. Lake Street 5. Bell Series #3 6. Perfumery 7. Mattress Factory 8. Tank (duet with a woman in a 500 gallon tank of water]
    - 4th Biennial, Feb. 27-Mar. 24, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 715)
    - 4th Biennial - artist contracts, Feb. 27-Mar. 24, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 716)
    - 4th Biennial - entry info, Feb. 27-Mar. 24, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 717)
    - Daria Dorosh/Erica Spitzer Rasmussen/Nancy E. Robinson, Mar. 27-Apr. 21, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 718)
    - "Tributary: Benefit Exhibition and Event Series", Apr. 24-May 19, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 719)
    - "Tributary: Benefit Exhibition and Event Series", Apr. 24-May 19, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 719a.)
    - Nana Olivas, Apr. 24-May 19, 2001[?] (Box 16, Folder 720)
    - Louise McCagg/Leah Oates, May 22-June 16, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 721)
    - Group Show: "...Her Infinite Variety..."/Heather Kinsinger, June 19-July 14, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 722)
      [nb: contains Iomega MAC100 zip disc; annotations on container: "!PLEASE RETURN! Ann Pachner 902 B'Way Suite 1607 #673 5686"; address also listed on disc itself, along with red sticker: "93536"]
    - "National Members Exhibition", Sep. 8-Oct. 6, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 723)
    - "National Members Exhibition"/Carol Ross, Oct. 9-Nov. 3, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 724)
    - Sylvia Netzer/Tomomi Maru Kanemaru, Nov. 6-Dec. 1, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 725)
    - "Eat Art 4", Dec. 2, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 726)
    - Regina Granne/JoAnne McFarland, Dec. 4-29, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 727)
    - Barbara Roux, "Society of Plants", Jan. 2-26, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 728)
    - "National Members Exhibition"/Joan Weber, Jan. 29-Feb. 23, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 729)
    - "Generations III", Feb. 24-Mar. 23, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 730)
    - Barbara Grinnell/Judy Cooper, Mar. 26-Apr. 20, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 731)
    - Nancy Storrow/Cinda Kelly, Apr. 23-May 18, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 732)
    - Ann Pachner/Georgette Sosin, May 21-June 15, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 733)
    - Members Group Show: "Wish You Were Here", June 18-July 13, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 734)
    - National Members Show: "New Space, New Work", Sep. 14-Oct. 5, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 735)
      [contains Kodak Infoguard CD-R Ultima 80, annotated: "New Space New Work" on front cover; disc surface, "A.I.R. Opening + Art work Sept 14/02"; on back cover, "Liz Surbeck Biddle Ivy Dachman Leila Daw Jane Gilmor Georgette Sosin Sue Hettmansperger Claire Wolf Krantz Carol Kumata Mo Neil Kathleen Schneider A.I.R. Gallery 511 West 25th Street NYC, NY 10001 Opening Sept. 14/02"]
    - Beatrice Riese/Carol Struve, Oct. 8-Nov. 2, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 736)
      [contains TDK 80 min/700 MB CD-R, picture index on front cover of jewel case with four Beatrice Riese drawings (dated 9-23-02), no annotations on disc]
    - Ursula Schneider/Heather Kinsinger, Nov. 5-30, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 737)
    - Luisa Sartori/Rosemary Meza, Dec. 3, 2002-Jan. 4, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 738)
    - Fellowship Retrospective Show/Gloria Klein, Jan. 7-Feb. 1, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 739)
    - Fifth Biennial, Mar. 4-29, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 740)
    - Susan Bee, Apr. 1-26, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 741)
    - Mimi Oritsky/Ann Schaumburger, Apr. 29-May 24, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 742)
    - "condition:human", Sep. 9-Oct. 4, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 743)
    - Barbara Bachner, Jan. 6-31, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 744)
    - "Generations.04", Mar. 2-26, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 745)
    - "The Current: Celebrating the 9th Year Reunion of 494 Gallery", Apr. 27-May 22, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 746)
    - "Aftermath" (curator: Barbara Zucker)/"Constructions", May 25-June 19, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 747)
    - "Lo intimo es lo universel: paintings and assemblages", May 26-June 17, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 748)
    - "Talking Hands: Annual Asian American Women Artists Alliance Group Exhibition", July 20-Aug. 7, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 749)
    - "George W. Bush Coloring Book Art Show", Aug. 29-Sep. 2, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 750)
    - Andrea Fahrman, Oct. 12-Nov. 6, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 751)
    - Regina Granne/Hilda O'Connell, Nov. 9-Dec. 4, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 752)
    - 6th Biennial, Mar. 8-Apr. 2, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 753)
    - "The Water Carriers", May 31-June 25, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 754)
    - "I.D.:id"/"Wish You Were Here: Artists' Postcard Show", June 29-July 23, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 755)
    - Diyan Achjadi/Jennifer Linton/Lindsey Moore, July 29-Sept. 3, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 756)
    - Francie Shaw/Ann Schaumburger/Mary Mount, Sep. 11-Oct. 9, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 757)
    - Jinnine Pak/Luisa Sartori/Liz Biddle, Nov. 8-Dec. 3, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 758)
  - Subseries B: Exhibitions held elsewhere
    - Vassar College Art Gallery: "Seven American Women: The Depression Decade", Jan. 19-Mar. 5, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 759)
    - PS1, New York City: "Overview 1972-1777: An Exhibition in Two Parts", Mar. 5-Apr. 19, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 760)
    - Ginza Kaigakan, Japan: "Works of A.I.R. Artists", Mar. 28-Apr. 28, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 761)
    - The Commission on the Status of Women: "A.I.R. Fair", June 8-July 7, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 762)
    - The Commission on the Status of Women: "A.I.R. Fair", June 8-July 7, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 763)
    - Franklin and Marshall College, Lancaster, PA: "Five Artists Changing", Oct. 26-Nov. 20, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 764)
    - HBO: "Contemporary Abstract Painting: An Alternative View", Feb. 1980[?] (Box 17, Folder 765)
    - McIntosh/Drysdale Gallery, Washington, D.C.: "Structure, Narrative, Decoration", Nov. 15-Dec. 11, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 766)
    - Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art, Ridgefield, CT: "New Dimensions in Drawing 1950-1980" (artwork loaned from A.I.R.), May 3-Sep. 6, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 767)
    - Douglass College, Rutgers University, New Brunswick, NJ: "The Women's Art Movement" (co-hosted with A.I.R.), June 6-26, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 768)
    - Lunds Konsthall, Sweden: "A.I.R. Members Show", Oct. 3-Nov. 1, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 769)
    - Helen Shlien Gallery, Boston, MA: "A.I.R. Group Show", Oct. 7-31, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 770)
    - Kean College, Union, NJ: "Cooperative Galleries" show, Nov. 17-Dec. 20, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 771)
    - American Indian Community House, Inc., NYC: "Native American Women Artists", June 4-22, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 772)
    - Muse Foundation, Philadelphia, PA: "Women's Expressive Lives, pt. III: Artists at the Frontiers", Apr. 23-May 22, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 773)
    - NYC: Ten Downtown Show, Fall, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 774)
    - Soho20 Gallery, NYC: "Blacklisted/Whitewashed/Redhanded", Dec. 11, 1990-Jan. 5, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 775)
    - The Drawing Center, NYC: "Cultural Economies: Histories from the Alternative Arts Movement", Feb. 24-Apr. 6, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 776)
    - The Arsenal, NYC: "Women's Work", Mar. 5-29, 1996" (Box 18, Folder 777)
    - Kingsborough Community College, Brooklyn, NY: "25 Years of A.I.R.", Feb. 11-Mar. 25, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 778)
    - Canessa Gallery, San Francisco, CA: "A.I.R. Gallery Group Show", Apr. 5-30, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 779)
    - Whitney Museum/PS1: "Women in Nature, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 780)
    - Misc. non-A.I.R.-related exhibits featuring A.I.R.-affiliated artists, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 781)
- Series IV: Photos/slides
  This series contains photographs and slides of A.I.R. exhibitions or of artworks by individual artists. The structure of the subseries remains faithful to the A.I.R. photo and slide inventory as it arrived at the Fales Library. The numbering system used by A.I.R. has been kept intact and is noted in the finding aid below. Subseries U consists of photographs and slides that were not part of the initial photos/slides series, but were received later as ancillary material. Subseries V consists of the A.I.R. Slide Registry, which was kept onsite at the Gallery as a resource for curators and other artists. The names listed in the finding aid for each binder does not comprise a complete list of the contents of that binder.
  Some folders in the SLIDE subseries contain no slides, reflecting that slide sleeves were empty when collection was accessioned at Fales.
  - Subseries A: A-0 PHOTO
    - Artist/Event: A.I.R. Gallery Members + Events --97 Wooster St. --1972 founding members + gallery opening (Box 18, Folder 782)
      Old number: A - 0 - (1- ) 1
      Contents: 8 photos
      Photo credit: Dotty Attie / Joan Switzer
    - Artist/Event: A.I.R. Gallery Members + Events --63 Crosby St. (Box 18, Folder 782A.)
      Old number: A - 0 - (1- ) 2
      Photo credit: Mary Beth Edelson
    - Artist/Event: Gerda Meyer Bernstein (Box 18, Folder 783)
      Old number: none
      Contents: 1 photo
      Photo credit: unknown
    - Artist/Event: Darla Bjork (Box 18, Folder 784)
      Contents: 2 photos
    - Artist/Event: Mary Grigoriadis (Box 18, Folder 785)
    - Artist/Event: Akiko Kotani (Box 18, Folder 786)
      Contents: 4 photos
      Photo credit: Carole Starz
    - Artist/Event: Jenny Nellis (Box 18, Folder 787)
      Contents: 3 photos
    - Artist/Event: Donna Byars (Box 18, Folder 788)
  - Subseries B: A-I PHOTO
    - Artist/Event: Rachel bas-Cohain / Member from 1972 - (Box 18, Folder 789)
      Old number: A - I - 1 - (1- )
      Contents: 75 photos
      Photo credit: Rachel bas-Cohain; Mary Beth Edelson; D. James Dee
    - Artist/Event: Sari Dienes / Member from 1978 - (Box 18, Folder 790)
      Old number: A - I - 2 - (1- )
      Photo credit: Warren Zuglese(?)
    - Artist/Event: Jane Haskell / Member from 1988 - 1994 (Box 18, Folder 791)
      Old number: A - I - 3 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: Pat Lasch / Member from 1974 - (Box 18, Folder 792)
      Old number: A - I - 4 - (1- )
      Contents: 5 photos
      Photo credit: Steven Sloman
    - Artist/Event: Rochelle Shicoff / Member: 1985 - (Box 18, Folder 793)
      Old number: A - I - 5 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: Sylvia Sleigh / Member from 1975 - 1978 (Box 18, Folder 794)
      Old number: A - I - 6 - (1- )
      Contents: 12 photos
      Photo credit: Geoffrey Clements; Joyce Ravid
    - Artist/Event: Elizabeth Munro Smith / Member: 1988 - 1994 (Box 18, Folder 795)
      Old number: A - I - 7 - (1- )
      Contents: 20 photos
      Photo credit: D. James Dee
    - Artist/Event: Susan L. Williams (Box 18, Folder 796)
      Photo credit: Linda Jane Gustas
  - Subseries C: A-II PHOTO
    - Artist/Event: 4/24 - 5/19, 1976 / Maude Boltz (Box 18, Folder 797)
      Old number: A - II - 1 - (1- )
      Contents: 12 photos (inc. her photos of other A.I.R. artists' work)
      Photo credit: Maude Boltz
    - Artist/Event: 9/6 - 9/22, 1979 / Artists from Israel: Six Women Artists (Box 18, Folder 798)
      Old number: A - II - 2 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: 11/27 - 12/15, 1979 / Laurace James (Box 18, Folder 799)
      Old number: A - II - 3 - (1- )
      Contents: 0 photos
    - Artist/Event: 2/5 - 2/9, 1980 / Women Artists Performance Series: Mimi Smith (Box 18, Folder 800)
      Old number: A - II - 4 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: 9/2 - 9/20, 1980 / Dialectics of Isolation: An Exhibit of Third World Women Artists of the US (Box 18, Folder 801)
      Old number: A - II - 5 - (1- )
      Contents: 18 photos
      Photo credit: Lydia Okumura; Martin W. Kane; Bev Buchanan; Larry Brown; Zarina; Barbara McCullough; Ken Petersen; Linda Eber; S.P.A.R.C.
    - Artist/Event: 6/8 - 6/26, 1982 / View from Upstate (Curator: Loretta Dunkelman) (Box 18, Folder 802)
      Old number: A - II - 6 - (1- )
      Photo credit: Nancy Lloyd
    - Artist/Event: 9/28 - 10/16, 1982 / Women Choose Men: An Invitational Show of Works by Men (Box 18, Folder 803)
      Old number: A - II - 7 - (1- )
      Photo credit: Sydney Cash; Leslie Harris
    - Artist/Event: 11/30 - 12/18, 1982 / Choice, Too: A.I.R. National Affiliate Member Exhibition (Box 18, Folder 804)
      Old number: A - II - 8 - (1- )
      Contents: 6 photos
    - Artist/Event: 1/11 - 1/29, 1983 / Louise Kramer (Box 18, Folder 805)
      Old number: A - II - 9 - (1- )
      Photo credit: Linda Cohen
    - Artist/Event: 9/6 - 9/24, 1983 / Kazuko (Box 18, Folder 806)
      Old number: A - II - 10 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: 11/29 - 12/17, 1983 / Barbara Strasen (Box 18, Folder 807)
      Old number: A - II - 11 - (1- )
      Photo credit: Barbara Strasen
    - Artist/Event: 4/24 - 5/12, 1984 / Judith Bernstein (Box 18, Folder 808)
      Old number: A - II - 12 - (1- )
      Photo credit: Judith Bernstein
    - Artist/Event: 11/6 - 11/24, 1984 / 4th A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Exhibition (Box 18, Folder 809)
      Old number: A - II - 13 - (1- )
  - Subseries D: A-III PHOTO
    - Artist/Event: 12/19, 1984 - 1/5, 1985 / 4th Holiday Invitational Exhibition (Box 18, Folder 810)
      Old number: A - III - 1 - (1- )
      Contents: 15 photos
    - Artist/Event: 10/8 - 10/26, 1985 / Gerda Meyer Bernstein (Box 18, Folder 811)
      Old number: A - III - 2 - (1- )
      Contents: 11 photos
      Photo credit: Gerda Meyer Bernstein
    - Artist/Event: 1/7 - 1/25, 1986 / Five Artists: A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Exhibition (Box 18, Folder 812)
      Old number: A - III - 3 - (1- )
      Photo credit: Edward Balassanian; Bill Redic
    - Artist/Event: 4/22 - 5/10, 1986 / Sarah Draney (Box 18, Folder 813)
      Old number: A - III - 4 - (1- )
      Photo credit: eeva-inkeri
    - Artist/Event: 3/31 - 4/18, 1987 / Donna Byars (Box 18, Folder 814)
      Old number: A - III - 5 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: 3/14 - 4/1, 1989 / Gerda Meyer Bernstein/Mary Barringer/ Diane Barwarski (Box 18, Folder 815)
      Old number: A - III - 6 - (1- )
      Contents: 13 photos
  - Subseries E: A-IV
    - Artist/Event: Gerda Meyer Bernstein (Box 18, Folder 816)
      Contents: 46 photos
    - Artist/Event: Ivy Dachman (Box 18, Folder 817)
      Contents: 7 photos
    - Artist/Event: Leila Daw (Box 18, Folder 818)
    - Artist/Event: Jessie Nebraska Gifford (Box 18, Folder 819)
      Contents: 24 photos
    - Artist/Event: Louise Kramer (Box 18, Folder 820)
      Contents: 27 photos
    - Artist/Event: Georgette Sosin (Box 18, Folder 821)
  - Subseries F: A-V PHOTO
    - Artist/Event: Diyan Achjadi (Box 18, Folder 822)
    - Artist/Event: Nancy Azara (Box 18, Folder 823)
    - Artist/Event: Stephanie Bernheim (Box 18, Folder 824)
      Contents: 16 photos
    - Artist/Event: Maude Boltz (Box 19, Folder 825)
      Contents: 14 photos
    - Artist/Event: Jane Gilmor (Box 19, Folder 826)
      Contents: 21 photos
    - Artist/Event: Tanya Hartman (Box 19, Folder 827)
    - Artist/Event: Adrienne Heinrich (Box 19, Folder 828)
    - Artist/Event: Sue Hettmansperger (Box 19, Folder 829)
      Contents: 25 photos
    - Artist/Event: Ursula Kavanagh (Box 19, Folder 830)
    - Artist/Event: Mary Maughelli (Box 19, Folder 831)
      Contents: 10 photos
    - Artist/Event: Constance Merriman (Box 19, Folder 832)
      Contents: 23 photos
    - Artist/Event: Kathleen Schneider (Box 19, Folder 833)
    - Artist/Event: Georgette Sosin (Box 19, Folder 834)
    - Artist/Event: Faith Wilding (Box 19, Folder 835)
  - Subseries G: A-VI PHOTO
    - Artist/Event: Sheila Manion Artz (Box 19, Folder 836)
    - Artist/Event: Sharon Brant (Box 19, Folder 837)
    - Artist/Event: Debra Hampton (Box 19, Folder 838)
    - Artist/Event: Juri Kim (Box 19, Folder 839)
      Contents: 5 postcards
    - Artist/Event: Tenesh Webber (Box 19, Folder 840)
  - Subseries H: B-I SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: Dotty Attie / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 39; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 841)
      Old number: B - I - 1 - (1- )
      Contents: 42 slides
    - Artist/Event: Rachel bas-Cohain / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 84; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 842)
      Old number: B - I - 2 - (1- )
      Contents: 186 slides, 1 negative filmstrip
      Photo credit: Edward Claycomb
    - Artist/Event: Judith Bernstein / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 3; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 843)
      Old number: B - I - 3 - (1- )
      Contents: 1 slide, 1 paper: "D. Desir-Davis The Drawing Center artist: J. Bernstein"
    - Artist/Event: Blythe Bohnen / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 17; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 844)
      Old number: B - I - 4 - (1- )
      Contents: 17 slides
    - Artist/Event: Maude Boltz / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 36; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 845)
      Old number: B - I - 5 - (1- )
      Contents: 41 slides
    - Artist/Event: Donna Byars / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 25; ** Member from 1978 - (Box 19, Folder 846)
      Old number: B - I - 6 - (1- )
      Contents: 28 slides
    - Artist/Event: Elisa d'Arrigo / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 4; ** Member from 1985 - (Box 19, Folder 847)
      Old number: B - I - 7 - (1- )
      Contents: 3 slides, 1 outslip: "Desir-Davis The Drawing Center artist: Elise D'Arrigo"
    - Artist/Event: Agnes Denes / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 18; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 848)
      Old number: B - I - 8 - (1- )
      Contents: 18 slides
    - Artist/Event: Sari Dienes / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 9; ** Member from 1978 - (Box 19, Folder 849)
      Old number: B - I - 9 - (1- )
      Contents: NO SLIDES.[slide sleeve empty when collection was accessioned.]
    - Artist/Event: Sarah Draney / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 33; ** Member from 1978 - (Box 19, Folder 850)
      Old number: B - I - 10 - (1- )
      Contents: 33 slides
    - Artist/Event: Loretta Dunkelman / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 48; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 851)
      Old number: B - I - 11 - (1- )
      Contents: 74 slides
  - Subseries I: B-II SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: Mary Beth Edelson / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 61; ** Member from 1975 - 1985; also participated in 1973 group exhibition. (Box 19, Folder 852)
      Old number: B - II - 1 - (1- )
      Contents: 59 slides, 2 outslips: "Desir-Davis Drawing Center artist: Mary Beth Edelson"; "Lannon Foundation"
    - Artist/Event: Sandra Eisenstein / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 1; ** Member from 1981 - (Box 19, Folder 853)
      Old number: B - II - 2 - (1- )
      Contents: NO SLIDES. [slide sleeve empty when collection was accessioned.]1 outslip: "Sandra Eisenstein [Three]"
    - Artist/Event: Mary Grigoriadis / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 21; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 854)
      Old number: B - II - 3 - (1- )
      Contents: 23 slides; 1 outslip: "Mary Grigoriadis Landscape 1985"
    - Artist/Event: Susan Hambleton / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 4; ** Member from 1986 - (Box 19, Folder 855)
      Old number: B - II - 4 - (1- )
      Contents: 8 slides, 1 outslip: "Susan Hambleton [Lampings] I"
    - Artist/Event: Harmony Hammond / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 1; ** Member from 1976 - (Box 19, Folder 856)
      Old number: B - II - 5 - (1- )
      Contents: NO SLIDES [slide sleeve empty when collection was accessioned.]
      Photo credit: N/A
    - Artist/Event: Jane Haskell / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 21; ** Member from 1988 - (Box 19, Folder 857)
      Old number: B - II - 6 - (1- )
      Contents: 28 slides, 1 outslip: "Desir-Davis Drawing Center - J. Haskell"
    - Artist/Event: Anne Healy / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 32; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 858)
      Old number: B - II - 7 - (1- )
      Contents: 32 slides, 1 outslip: "Anne Healy"
    - Artist/Event: Laurace James / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 17; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 859)
      Old number: B - II - 8 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: Kazuko / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 4; ** Member from 1995 - (Box 19, Folder 860)
      Old number: B - II - 9 - (1- )
      Contents: 2 slides, 1 outslip: "Kazuko"
    - Artist/Event: Pat Lasch / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 4; ** Member from 1974 - (Box 19, Folder 861)
      Old number: B - II - 10 - (1- )
      Contents: 1 slide, 1 outslip: "Pat Lasch"
    - Artist/Event: Ana Mendieta / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 13; ** Member from 1978 - [This folder contains no slides] (Box 19, Folder 862)
      Old number: B - II - 11 - (1- )
      Contents: NO SLIDES [slide sleeve empty when collection was accessioned.] 1 outslip: "Desir-Davis Drawing Center - Mendieta"
    - Artist/Event: Patsy Norvell / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides: 8; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 863)
      Old number: B - II - 12 - (1- )
      Contents: 8 slides, 1 outslip: "Desir-Davis Drawing Center - Patsy Norvell"
    - Artist/Event: Howardena Pindell / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides:; ** Member from 1972 - (Box 19, Folder 864)
      Old number: B - II - 13 - (1- )
      Contents: NO SLIDES. [slide sleeve empty when collection was accessioned.]
    - Artist/Event: Elizabeth Racette / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides:; ** Member from 1991 - (Box 19, Folder 865)
      Old number: B - II - 14 - (1- )
    - Artist/Event: Elaine Reichek / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides:; ** Member from 1981 - (Box 19, Folder 866)
      Old number: B - II - 15 - (1- )
      Contents: 8 slides, 1 outslip: "Elaine Reichek"
    - Artist/Event: Susan Hambleton / Member from 1986 - (Box 19, Folder 867)
  - Subseries J: B-III SLIDE
    - Artist/Event: Diane Samuels / Filing Date: September, 1995; Number of Slides:; ** Member from 1985 - (Box 19, Folder 868)